=The Shoufu Can Read Mind=
= الشوفو يستطيع قراءة العقل =
=Episode 3=
= الحلقة 3 =
Since I came here through this place,
منذ أن جئت إلى هنا من خلال هذا المكان ،
I should be able to go back here.
يجب أن أكون قادرًا على العودة إلى هنا.
Let me eat first.
دعني آكل أولاً.
No way.
مستحيل.
I can't swim.
لا أستطيع السباحة.
Also,
أيضًا،
I'm so young
أنا لازلت شاب
and so beautiful.
وجميلة جدا.
I haven't seen
أنا لم أر
handsome men enough.
وسيم بما فيه الكفاية.
Miss!
يفتقد!
Don't do that!
لا تفعل ذلك!
I was right for not jumping in.
كنت على حق لأنني لم أقفز.
I heard that
سمعت ان
General Shen's family
عائلة الجنرال شين
loves Shen Zhihuan.
يحب شين تشيهوان.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Miss,
يفتقد،
your question
سؤالك
is weird.
غريب.
Just answer me.
فقط أجبني.
Of course it's true.
بالطبع هذا صحيح.
Master and Madam Shen
سيد وسيدتي شن
treat you
يعاملك
as their precious.
ثمينة لهم.
Your brother
أخوك
can't bear to see
لا تتحمل الرؤية
you being bullied.
تتعرض للتخويف.
(It's the same as recorded in the book.)
(إنه نفس ما تم تسجيله في الكتاب.)
Is Shen family
هي عائلة شين
wealthy?
ثري؟
I'm not sure how much money
لست متأكدًا من مقدار المال
Shen family has.
عائلة شين لديها.
However,
لكن،
Master Shen is the general
السيد شين هو الجنرال
that's important to His Majesty.
هذا مهم لجلالة الملك.
I think
أظن
he's rich.
هو ثري.
The imperial examination is coming.
الامتحان الإمبراطوري قادم.
Yanqing,
يانكينغ ،
I remember you scored the highest
أتذكر أنك سجلت أعلى درجة
three years ago.
منذ ثلاثة أعوام.
In just a few years,
في غضون سنوات قليلة ،
you've become
لقد أصبحت
my important Grand Secretariat.
أمانتي الكبرى الهامة.
I want you
أريدك
to be in charge of the imperial examination.
ليكون مسؤولاً عن الامتحان الإمبراطوري.
The imperial court will be convinced.
سوف يقتنع البلاط الإمبراطوري.
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم يا صاحب الجلالة.
Also,
أيضًا،
I've read
أنا قد قرأت
the Censors' memorial.
النصب التذكاري للرقيب.
There will be people cheating
سيكون هناك أناس يغشون
in the imperial examination every year.
في الامتحان الإمبراطوري كل عام.
Therefore,
لذلك،
investigate in
التحقيق في
this imperial examination.
هذا الفحص الإمبراطوري.
If there's any cheater,
إذا كان هناك أي غشاش ،
whether
سواء
they're of the authority or the royal family,
هم من السلطة أو العائلة المالكة ،
you need to
أنت بحاجه إلى
punish them
معاقبتهم
and not let anyone go.
ولا تدع أي شخص يذهب.
Yes.
نعم.
(Divorce settlement agreement)
(اتفاقية تسوية الطلاق)
Miss,
(اتفاق تسوية الطلاق) آنسة ،
I've been serving you for so long.
لقد كنت أخدمك لفترة طويلة.
I didn't know that you can cook well.
لم أكن أعلم أنه يمكنك الطهي جيدًا.
Eat and stop talking.
أكل وتوقف عن الكلام.
Miss,
يفتقد،
you've been looking at it.
كنت تنظر إليه.
What are you trying to write?
ماذا تحاول ان تكتب؟
A divorce settlement agreement.
اتفاقية تسوية الطلاق.
A divorce settlement agreement?
اتفاق تسوية الطلاق؟
Sister, since you've decided to divorce,
أخت ، منذ أن قررت الطلاق ،
you should talk to Sir Xu
يجب عليك التحدث مع السير شو
as soon as possible.
في أسرع وقت ممكن.
After all, everyone knows that
بعد كل شيء ، الجميع يعرف ذلك
you were making
كنت تصنع
a scene
مشهد
and General Shen
والجنرال شين
was crying in front of His Majesty,
كان يبكي أمام جلالة الملك
His Majesty had no choice but to marry you to Sir Xu
لم يكن أمام جلالة الملك من خيار سوى أن يتزوجك من السير شو
and Sir Xu
والسير شو
had to obey and marry you.
اضطررت إلى طاعتك والزواج منك.
You...
أنت...
You're just a female hostess.
أنت مجرد مضيفة أنثى.
Why are you so arrogant?
لماذا أنت متعجرف جدا؟
You're cheap and lowly.
أنت رخيص ومتواضع.
Sir Xu will not like you.
السيد شو لن يحبك.
You...
أنت...
You can't do anything you like here.
لا يمكنك فعل أي شيء تريده هنا.
Also,
أيضًا،
I'm General Shen's daughter.
أنا ابنة الجنرال شين.
I only have a brother
ليس لدي سوى أخ
and no sister.
ولا أخت.
If you keep calling me
إذا واصلت الاتصال بي
"sister",
"أخت"،
it's not only hurting my ears,
إنه لا يؤذي أذني فقط ،
you'll also sound like you want to get something from us.
ستبدو أيضًا وكأنك تريد الحصول على شيء منا.
Why is it so happening here?
لماذا يحدث هذا هنا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
We didn't do anything.
لم نفعل أي شيء.
Madam Xu,
سيدتي شو ،
I'm cheap and lowly.
أنا رخيص ومتواضع.
I shouldn't have called you "sister".
لا ينبغي أن أدعوك "أخت".
I'm only here to thank you
أنا هنا فقط لأشكرك
for saving me.
لإنقاذي.
Please
لو سمحت
don't be mad at me.
لا تغضب مني.
(You're really good at acting.)
(أنت جيد حقًا في التمثيل.)
(You're above Academy Award.)
(أنت فوق جائزة الأوسكار).
You need to return the favour.
تحتاج إلى رد الجميل.
Kneel here!
ركع هنا!
You lowly servant!
أنت خادم حقير!
You're just a hostess
أنت مجرد مضيفة
and how dare you seduce my husband!
وكيف تجرؤ على إغواء زوجي!